It was a dark and stormy night
It looked like something out of a horror movie
Crumbling
Broken shut
As he opened the door
His heart pounded in anticipation
He could feel the tension in the air as he stepped into the hallways filled with strange objects
Text that seem to have a life of Their Own
Everywhere he looked
There were strange shadows and unfamiliar
This is coming from every corner of
The more Robert explored this Gloomy building
The more convinced he became
Best place held a dark secret
Next
Peculiar smell coming from inside
But it was in the back room where his real curiosity was sat
Hidden under stacks of books and ancient artifact
Robert was horrified as he read through these
Hysteria due to Superstition surrounding
Thousands of people believe they were cursed by
This is beyond their control and began accusing others of black magic and devil worship before these
Accusations eventually led to
At first Robert thought this was just
Ghostly activities in the antique
Suddenly it all
This shop served as an unintentional conduit
Creating waves of mass Hysteria